smashingeeks.com 2012-03-06

# Privacy Policy - SmashinGeeks

Privacy Policy

The privacy for our visitors and readers to **SmashinGeeks.com** is very important to us. At **SmashinGeeks.com** ,we recognize that privacy of your personal and additional information(s) is important. Below is the information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit or read at **SmashinGeeks.com** , and how we defend the info we recieve when you visit **SmashinGeeks.com**. We never share or sell your personal information to third parties.

#### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

#### Comments

We like comments, but any comments which is abusive, spread hatred, racial or any way hurting anyone’s opinion will never be entertained. We keep moderating privacy in our comment system to maintain the integrity of individuals.Email address mentioned in the comment form will always be use for privacy and never be used for spamming. Though we highly recommend never post your Email address into the comments, so that other can’t see it. Even if you post email address in comments, make sure you follow this format **admin[at]gmail.com**.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit and register at **SmashinGeeks.com**.You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

#### Advertisement policy

We use third party advertising company to serve advertisements. Some of them like Google Adsense uses the **DART cookie** to serve advertisement based on user interest and previous interaction. Though user can also of DART cookie settings by visiting the [Google Adsense Advertisement Privacy Policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

### Keywords:

third-party advertising company to serve advertisements
